{"id":"2017_24","name":"Romans Lesson 242017_24","memoryVerse":"“Love must be sincere. Hate what is evil; cling to what is good.” – Romans 12:9","dayQuestions":{"one":{"title":"FIRST DAY: Read the notes and the references.","questions":[{"id":"2017_24_1","questionText":"1. What was meaningful to you in the lecture?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_24_2","questionText":"2. What help did you receive from the notes?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"two":{"title":"SECOND DAY: Read Romans 13:1-5.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"13:1-5"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_24_3","questionText":"3.  Define “be subject to” or “submit.” Who is to submit to governing authorities, and why?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_24_4","questionText":"4.  Give reasons people struggle with submitting to authority? Which is your greatest struggle?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_24_5","questionText":"5.  Give examples of when refusing to submit to governing authority is acceptable in God’s eyes? (See Daniel 3 and 6; Acts 5:29)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Daniel","verse":"3:1-30"},{"book":"Daniel","verse":"6:1-28"},{"book":"Acts","verse":"5:29"}]}]},"three":{"title":"THIRD DAY: Read Romans 13:1-5.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"13:1-5"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_24_6","questionText":"6.  When you refuse to submit to moral and legal authority, against whom are you ultimately rebelling?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_24_7","questionText":"7. How does respect for authority glorify God?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_24_8","questionText":"8. How is God convicting you regarding these verses?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"four":{"title":"FOURTH DAY: Read Romans 13:3-5.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"13:3-5"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_24_9","questionText":"  9.  How are rulers God’s servants for good, even if they are evil? What comfort and confidence can you have when you receive evil instead of good from a leader?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_24_10","questionText":"10.  What reasons does Paul give for submitting to authorities? Can you think of other reasons?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_24_11","questionText":"11.  What kind of example do you set for your children and others who watch your response to governing authorities?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"five":{"title":"FIFTH DAY: Read Romans 13:6-7.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"13:6-7"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_24_12","questionText":"12.  What did Jesus say about paying taxes? (See Luke 20:22-25.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Luke","verse":"20:22-25"}]},{"id":"2017_24_13","questionText":"13.  What are the purposes of taxes? What should be your attitude toward paying them?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_24_14","questionText":"14.   From the following verses, list those to whom we are to show respect and honor.  What are some specific ways you can show respect or honor to these people?  Exodus 20:12","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Exodus","verse":"20:12"}]},{"id":"2017_24_14b","questionText":"14.   Leviticus 19:32","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Leviticus","verse":"19:32"}]},{"id":"2017_24_14c","questionText":"14.  1 Timothy 5:17","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"1 Timothy","verse":"5:17"}]},{"id":"2017_24_14d","questionText":"14.   1 Timothy 6:15b-16","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"1 Timothy","verse":"6:15-16"}]},{"id":"2017_24_14e","questionText":"14.   1 Peter 2:13-17","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"1 Peter","verse":"2:13-17"}]},{"id":"2017_24_15","questionText":"15. How can you show honor and respect to someone whose decisions and character differ from yours?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"six":{"title":"SIXTH DAY: Read Romans 13:1-7.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"13:1-7"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_24_16","questionText":"16.  What have you learned about God in this week’s study? How may your group pray for you as you make this truth a part of your life?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_24_17","questionText":"17. Homiletics for discussion and administrative leaders:  Romans 13:1-7","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"13:1-7"}]}]}}}